Hello.
السلام علیکم۔
I am a solo developer, Yeon Sam-heum.
میں ایک فردی ڈویلپر یونسام ہوم ہوں۔
For 17 years, I have been running a company,
میں نے 17 سال تک ایک کمپنی چلائی،
creating over 200 websites and 600,000 pages with AI.
AI کے ساتھ 200 سے زائد ویب سائٹس، 600,000 صفحات تیار کیے۔
This submission is not something newly created.
یہ پروڈکٹ نئی نہیں ہے۔
It is a tool that has grown over eight years — WIA Geulsalim.
یہ 8 سال کی محنت کا نتیجہ ہے — WIA Geulsalim۔
95% of humanity's 5,000 years of knowledge remains inaccessible.
انسانیت کے 5000 سال کے علم کا 95% ابھی بھی ناقابل رسائی ہے۔
87% of Korea's historical documents are still dormant, not digitised,
جنوبی کوریا کی تاریخی دستاویزات کا 87% ڈیجیٹلائز نہیں ہو سکی ہیں اور
and 97% of the 7,000 languages in the world lack quality AI translation and voice services.
دنیا کی 7000 زبانوں میں سے 97%، AI ترجمہ و صوتی معیار میں نمایاں کمی یا بالکل موجود نہیں ہیں۔
300 million individuals with sensory impairments still cannot touch books.
300 ملین بصری معذور افراد اب بھی کتابوں کو چھونے سے قاصر ہیں۔
These four barriers must be overcome simultaneously.
یہ 4 اکٹھے رکاوٹیں ایک دفعہ میں حل ہونی چاہئیں۔
Geulsalim operates on a four-step pipeline — restoration, structuring, conversion, and delivery.
Geulsalim کا 4 مرحلوں کا پائپ لائن — بحالی · ساخت · تبدیل · ترسیل۔
From now on, I will show you through four demos.
اب میں آپ کو چار ڈیمو کے ذریعے براہ راست دکھاؤں گا۔
The first demo — restoration.
پہلا ڈیمو — بحالی ہے۔
A Diffusion model restores damaged historical documents, and a language model infers missing characters.
Diffusion ماڈل خراب شدہ تاریخی دستاویزات کی بحالی کرتا ہے، زبان ماڈل غائب حروف کا اندازہ لگاتا ہے۔
Restoration is not manipulation.
بحالی تدلیس نہیں ہے۔
The original hash is permanently preserved.
اصل ہیش کو مستقل طور پر محفوظ کیا جاتا ہے۔
The second demo — structuring.
دوسرا ڈیمو — ساخت ہے۔
AI automatically structures a tag-less PDF into WCAG 2.2 compliant HTML, even generating alternative text.
ٹیگ کے بغیر PDF کو WCAG 2.2 کے مطابق HTML میں، AI خود بخود ترتیب دیتا ہے اور متبادل متن تک تیار کرتا ہے۔
On the WIA Book accessibility testing site, I am already automatically checking 80 items.
WIA Book رسائی جانچ کی سائٹ پر، میں پہلے ہی 80 اشیاء کی خودکار جانچ کر رہا ہوں۔
The third demo — EPUB accessibility restoration.
تیسرا ڈیمو — EPUB کی رسائی کی بحالی ہے۔
It automatically restores non-compliant EPUB 2 to EPUB 3.
EPUB 2 جو کہ رسائی کی کمی کا شکار ہے، کو خودکار طور پر EPUB 3 میں بحال کیا جاتا ہے۔
It passes all 80 inspection items.
80 جانچ اشیاء کو مکمل طور پر کامیاب ہوتا ہے۔
WCAG, EPUB A11y, KS X 6201, European EAA — it meets four international standards simultaneously.
WCAG، EPUB A11y، KS X 6201، یورپی EAA — چار بین الاقوامی معیارات کو simultaneouly پورا کرتا ہے۔
The fourth demo — multimodal delivery.
چوتھا ڈیمو — کثیرالابعاد ترسیل ہے۔
7,000 languages in Braille, 254 languages in voice,
براہ راست 7000 برلنگ زبانیں، 254 صوتی زبانیں،
WIA Talk 3D sign language, 436 interactive tools and simulators.
WIA Talk 3D اشارہ زبان، 436 بات چیت کے اوزار اور سیمولیٹرز۔
WIA Live enables deaf and visually impaired individuals to communicate directly without an interpreter,
بصری معذور اور سن Hearing impaired افراد بغیر مترجم براہ راست بات چیت کرنے کے لئے WIA Live،
and it is already in trial operation.
دراصل کارکردگی میں ہے۔
Our Geulsalim.
ہماری Geulsalim۔
弘益人間 — benefiting all people while being sustainable. We're Geulsalim.
弘益人間 — سب کے لیے مفید، لیکن پائیدار۔ We're Geulsalim.